{
    "subject": "resource/Tibet_(1912\u201351)",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Lhasa",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Tibet (1912\u201351) is Lhasa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9549624919891357,
            "question": "During what years was Lhasa the capital of Tibet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9158771634101868,
            "question": "Is Lhasa still the capital of Tibet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784399628639221,
            "question": "What was the capital of Tibet between 1912 and 1951?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7605059742927551,
            "question": "What is the significance of Lhasa in Tibetan history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6600773930549622,
            "question": "Name a significant event that took place in Lhasa during its time as capital."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.59268718957901,
            "question": "Where is Lhasa located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4517590403556824,
            "question": "Can you describe the cultural heritage of Lhasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.355264276266098,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks or attractions in Lhasa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3549143075942993,
            "question": "What is the current status of Tibet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15400782227516174,
            "question": "How did Lhasa's political status change after 1951?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Tibet (1912\u201351) is Lhasa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9240_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the current status of Tibet?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9240_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable landmarks or attractions in Lhasa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9240_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the cultural heritage of Lhasa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9240_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9240_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The capital of Tibet (1912-51) is Lhasa.\" The details in the provided texts describe Lhasa as the capital of the Tibet Autonomous Region and mention its historical significance, including its role during the unified period under Songtsen Gampo."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Before Lhasa became the capital of Tibet Autonomous Region, Shannan held that role.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}